Indiana History mss., 1725-1973 LMC 1544 LMC 1544
Lilly Library
- Indiana History
  - Skelcher, Mrs. Lucille Detraz, Vevay, Ind. Further notes on the descendants of the Dumonts., 1939, Feb. 16 -; Typed Document 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Accompanied by 2 Letters Signed Skelcher, Mrs. Lucille Detraz, Vevay, Ind. To William O. Lynch, editor, Indiana Magazine of History, Feb. 16 & 23, 1939; and 1p. of notes "Descendants of Julie Louisa Dumont." (A.D.)
  - Sackett, Homer Eddy, 1875-1966, judge. Gary, Indiana. To Henry R. Sackett, Sackett, Pyatt & Waitkus, 569 Broadway, Gary, Indiana. Biographical sketch., 1939, Apr. 11 -; Xerox copy of Typed Letter Signed 12 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Steele, Selma Neubacher, 1870-1945, art teacher. The house of the singing winds. Reminiscences of social life and customs in Brown County, Indiana, and Theodore Clement Steele., 1940, Jan.-1941, Feb. 26 -; Autograph Document Signed [237] p. 27 cm. (Bound 54)
    Four parts.
    Published with editorial changes; omission of quotations which preceded each part; many deletions especially in part III; and extensive rearrangement in part III.
    Indianapolis, Indiana Historical Society, 1966, pp. 55-172.
    Another draft of the manuscript is located in the Indiana Historical Society Library in Indianapolis, Indiana (Annual Report 1974/75 page 30).
  - Bryan, William Lowe, 1860-1955, I. U. president. Bloomington, Indiana. To Martha Evelyn (Thrasher) Shideler. Thanks Mrs. Shideler for her "faithful & efficient service.", 1940, June 16 -; Autograph Letter Signed 1 p. 17.5 cm. (Box 3)
    Mrs. Shideler, a nurse, cared for Mrs. Bryan during an illness.
  - Downing, Arthur C., pres.; James Whitcomb Riley Old Home Society, Greenfield, Ind. To Herman B Wells, pres., Indiana University, Bloomington, Ind. Letter carried on first trip of the New York Central's streamlined train, James Whitcomb Riley., 1941, Apr. 28 -; Autograph Letter Signed 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - South, Mary Ellis, 1880-1968, Indianapolis, Ind. To Marion Hunter (Weinstein) Gray, Terre Haute, Ind. Gives information on Theodore Dreiser and Paul Dresser., 1942, July 7 -; Typed Letter Signed 4 p. 20 cm. (Box 3)
    Accompanied by cover.
    Gift. 1964
  - Shields, Robert William, 1918-, author. 648 East Monroe Street, Franklin, Indiana. To Robert G. Miller. Seeks information on the Reno gang., 1943, Mar. 31 -; Typed Letter Signed, 3 items, 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Accompanied by Robert G. Miller to Robert William Shields, 1943, April 1, 1943.
    Information on the Reno gang.
    Typed Letter Signed (carbon) 1 p. 28 cm.
    Included in a printed broadside advertising The Life of John Reno of Seymour, Indiana, edited by Robert William Shields, with holograph notes.
  - M'Coy, John, 1782-1859, Baptist deacon. Extracts from the diaries of John M'Coy of Clark County, Indiana, ed. with an introduction and explanation in notes by Elizabeth Hayward., 1943 -; Typed Document 19 p. 28 cm. (Bound 55)
    Purchase. 1943
  - Inwood, David, 1927-2008. Two photograph and scrapbook albums, 1944-1948
    Purchase: 2023. House of Mirth Photos (Stacy Waldman).
    Biographical / Historical
    David William Inwood was born in South Bend, Indiana, in 1927. He graduated from Central High School in South Bend in 1944 and served in Japan in 1946. After the war, he attended Indiana University. He married Kathryn Goodman in 1951; together they had 4 children. He passed away in South Bend in 2008.
    Japan -- History -- Allied occupation, 1945-1952
    - Civilian album, June 1944-December 1948
      "The contents of [Inwood's] civilian life album include lots of photos, ephemera and newspaper clippings from his time at Purdue University and, after returning from Japan, Indiana University. It seems that David Inwood was of the Inwood family of [Inwoods Grocery] in South Bend, Indiana (included in the album is a photo of the storefront from the street). There are snapshot photos and nice portraits of girls and friends, friends' weddings turned to young families, outings around Indiana, campus photos, a trick/double exposure (he was part of the photography club!), a sculpture show at his art center, his friends with their '41 Chevy and '48 Studebaker convertible. Fun ephemera from this time include: his best bowling game scoresheets while at Purdue, university maps, class schedule, ID card booklet, draft registration booklet, a pocket-sized honorable discharge certificate, brochures from proms, matchbooks from Indiana, a lost and found posting in the newspaper with 'got back' written on it, a 1947 clipping of an anti-discrimination opinion piece in the Indiana University newspaper as well as other events and jokes, a diploma in Pinballogy from Dixie Bar-B-Q, stock certificate in The Pine, Inc., etc."
      --Bookseller description, House of Mirth photos
    - Army life album, March 1946-March 1947
      "The album starts with photos of the Barracks at Ft. Warren in Cheyenne, Wyoming. Included is his rejected application to become an army officer--he joined the transportation corps instead, and was a radio operator. He attended training for Transportation Corps in Denver, Colorado (where he writes he took a whole day off work to hitchhike to Estes Park in Colorado just to take pictures of the scenery!). Other photos in the states include a train to California, Camp Stoneman in California, and later a return to Missoula, Montana. In 1946 he deployed to Osaka, Japan. Included are many photos of Osaka--from rooftops, to city streets, to buildings reduced to rubble, and the 25 Club (a favorite hang-out). Also pictured include: Johnson Field (first concrete airstrip in Japan built by US Army), airplanes on the field (and some nudie paintings on the skybirds), "maneuvers" in Toyooka and Yokosuka (he participated in an 'amphibious maneuver' in Yokosuka, photos of these ocean views and a newspaper clipping included as well), Enoshima Island Buddhist statues and shrines, a racist caption of a country man and ox-drawn 'honey wagon' (included are several newspaper cartoons poking fun at honey wagons), Tokyo city views, stray cats, a street parade, Osaka Castle, Kyoto, planted fields, more 'bombed out' rubble, Nara, Wakayama, children gathered around an army fire in the cold in Kobe, Yokohama Harbor, and departing via ship."
      --Bookseller's description, House of Mirth Photos
  - Anderson, Mrs. Marguerite H., librarian.; Indiana State Library, Indianapolis, Indiana. To Vincennes Public Library. Vincennes, Indiana. Refers to the first issue of the Indiana Gazette., 1946, May 1 -; Typescript 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Purcell, George W., postmaster, Bloomington, Indiana. To Robert A. Simpson. Vincennes, Indiana. Relates to the Indiana Gazette., 1946, May 14 -; Typescript 4 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Stevens, Alice D. to Russo, Dorothy, 1947, Nov 19 (Box 3)
    Letter from Alice D. Stevens, librarian at Logansport Public Library, to Dorothy Russo of the Hoosier Bookshop, Indianapolis, Indiana, regarding William D. Owens, born in Bloomington, Indiana, September 6, 1846.
  - Peters, R. Earl. The Plush Horse, ca. 1948 - (Bound 56)
  - Caswell, Omar, -1959, Oldest church building in Hart township, Warrick County, Ind., 1948 -; Typed Document 5 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    p. 3-5: The founding of Eby, Indiana.
    Accompanied by photograph of church.
  - Rogers, Bruce, 1870-1957, book designer. RFD3 Danbury, Connecticut. To Mrs. Dorothy (Ritter) Russo. "… sending you a little pamphlet I recently printed for the Portfolio Club… a minute speck in the history of Indiana…", 1952, Oct. 29 -; Autograph Letter Signed 1 p. 15 cm. (Box 3)
    Transferred from Reader's Services, Lilly Library. 1977
  - Garman, Harry Otto, 1880-1952, engineer. Biography: James Franklin Hanly, 1863-1920, governor of Indiana, 1905-1909., Typescript of Autograph Document Signed 97 pp. 29 cm. (Bound 57)
    Two copies of typescript made in the Department of Special Collections, Indiana University Library, 1952, from original lent by the author.
  - Garman, Harry Otto, 1880-1952, engineer. Biography (unbound manuscript): James Franklin Hanly, 1863-1920, governor of Indiana, 1905-1909 (Box 3)
  - Lanier, Reginald B., Financier. New York, New York. To Thomas Powderly Martin, Bloomington, Indiana. Knows of no surviving records of James Franklin Doughty Lanier or of the partnership, Winslow, Lanier & Co.; history of Winslow, Lanier & Co., 1953, Feb. 10 -; Autograph Letter Signed 3 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Mayer, Mrs. Maybelle C. (Pettigrew), (Mrs. Walter R. Mayer), business woman. The Woman's Rotary Club of Indianapolis, organized April 28, 1919., 1953, Aug. 8 -; Typed Document 3 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Signed: A. McC. H. for M.C.P.M. 8-8-53 and Agnes Hanna for Mrs. W. R. Mayer, founder.
  - Nickey, Samuel, 1868-, lumberman. Oral history interview with Samuel Nickey, Sr., Memphis, Tennessee, by John Larson., 1953, Dec. -; Typed Document [1], 1-3, 5-9 p. 28 cm.; copy. (Box 3)
    Interviewed for Forest History Foundation, Inc., St. Paul, Minnesota.
  - Bray, William Gilmer, 1903-1979, congressman. Washington, D.C. To Martin David Dubin, Bloomington, Ind. Transcribed radio programs and newsletters to reach voters of Seventh Indiana district., 1954, Apr. 9 -; Copy of Typed Letter Signed 2 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Typescript made in the Manuscript division of the Library from the original lent by Martin David Dubin. 1956
  - Bray, William Gilmer, 1903-1979, congressman. Washington, D.C. To Martin David Dubin, Bloomington, Ind. Questionaire on the Indo-China situation., 1954, June 16 -; Copy of Typed Letter Signed 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Typescript made in the Manuscript division of the Indiana University Library from the original lent by Martin David Dubin. 1956
  - Garten, James E., fl. 1956. [Memoir of Clarksburg and early Odon, Indiana.], Typed Carbon [2], 90, 3, [1] p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Typescript made in President's office, Indiana University, from original lent by author.
    Accompanied by copy of Herman B Wells, To James E. Garten, September 1, 1956.
  - Sonderman, Albert F., Ferdinand, Indiana. To Elfrieda Wilhelmina Henrietta Lang, Bloomington, Indiana. Biographical information on Alois Gustave Wollenmann and Matthias Kempf, physicians., 1957, Jan. 24 -; Letter Signed 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Gift. 1957
  - Lane, Russell Adrian, 1897-1986, educator. A History of Segregation and Integration in the Indianapolis Public Schools from 1847 to 1960., 1960, Mar. 1 -; Copy of Typed Document [140] p.; 25 x 29 cm. (Box 3)
    In a loose-leaf binder.
    Accompanied by other loose papers, 1963-1968, printed.
  - Hawken, Henry A., 1940-, Indiana University student. The speaking of Henry Smith Lane, 1834-1856 … Submitted to the faculty of the graduate school in partial fulfillment of the requirements for the degree of Master of arts in the Department of speech and theatre, Indiana University, August 1963., 1963, Aug. -; Typed Document viii, 74 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Delta Kappa Gamma society, Alpha Epsilon state, Indiana. Biographies of pioneer women educators, … Indiana. Positive microfilm of original papers in the library of Delta Kappa Gamma film society, International, 416 West Twelfth Street, Austin 1, Texas., 1963-1965 -; 1 Reel; genreform: microfilm. (Box 3)
  - Feightner, Harold C., 1892-1969, executive, 718 Chamber of Commerce Bldg., Indianapolis, Indiana. 150 years of brewing in Indiana, the story of politics, prohibition, and patronage., 1964 -; Mimeographed Document, [210], [15] p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - South, Mary Ellis, 1880-1968. 60 South 20th street, Terre Haute, Indiana. To Isabel Louise Downing. Miss South explains that "Paul Dresser wrote 'The Banks of the Wabash' at Mudlavia Springs in the hotel there.", 1966, Feb. 7 -; Autograph Letter Signed 2 p. 19.6 cm. (Box 3)
  - Branigin, Roger Douglas, 1902-, governor of Indiana. Speech on the Indiana sesquicentennial exhibit in the Lilly Library delivered in the reading room, Lilly Library, Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana., 1966, Nov. 28 -; Tape recording. 1 reel. 6 1/4 inches. 3 3/4 inches per second. (Box 9)
    Duration: 35 minutes.
    The Governor's speech was 15 1/2 minutes; the introduction of the Governor by President Stahr 6 minutes and remarks after the speech 11 3/4 minutes; and remarks by Dr. Byrd 1 3/4 minutes.
  - Delta Kappa Gamma society, Alpha Epsilon state, Indiana. Biographies of pioneer women educators,…Indiana. Positive microfilm of original papers in the library of Delta Kappa Gamma society, International, 416 West Twelfth Street, Austin 1, Texas., 1966-1969 -; 1 Reel microfilm. (Box 3)
  - Bowen, Otis Ray, 1918-, physician, governor of Indiana. Message to the Indiana General Assembly convening in Joint Session., 1973, Jan. 24 -; Typed Document, 2 items, 33 p. 28 cm.; copy. (Box 3)
    Accompanied by letter from Bowen to Cecil K. Byrd, Feb. 9, 1973.
    Gift. 1973
  - Carroll, Patrick Dunstan, 1941-, lawyer.; Senate, State of Indiana, Indianapolis, Indiana, 46204 To Geneva Hitchcock Warner, 1316 South Stull, Bloomington, Indiana, 47401. Concerns Senate Bill 266 which maintains the zero phosphate ban on laundry detergents., 1973, Mar. 14 -; Typed Letter Signed 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Mickey, Rosie (Cheatham), 1939-, teacher. Russell Adrian Lane: Biography of an Urban Negro School Administrator., 1983, May -; Copy of Typed Document 275 pp. 27.3 cm. (Bound 58)
    Bound in black.
    Pages 21, 188, and 275: references to Lilly Library material.
    Ph.D. dissertation at the University of Akron, Ohio.
  - Allen, Mary Moore, Goldsboro, North Carolina. Origins of names of army and air corps posts, camps, and stations in World War II in Indiana., Typed Document 24 p. 24 cm. (Box 3)
  - Andrew, Mrs. Elizabeth (Wheeler). William P. Wheeler: [A biographical sketch], Autograph Document Signed 5 p. 26-36 cm. (Box 3)
  - Ball, Elisabeth Woodworth 1897-1982, collector. To Ruth Elizabeth Adomeit "I have had two very nice things happen, one a four day trip down and along the Ohio…Then we had a very large orchid show…", Autograph Letter Signed [2] p. 24.3 cm. (Box 3)
    Accompanied by letter of transmittal from Ruth Adomeit to Lilly Librarian, W. R. Cagle, Mar. 31, 1993.
    Gift. 1993
  - Birch, Jessee Setlington, Oxford, Indiana. The grand prairie [particularly that section of it which lies in Benton County, Indiana]., Typed Document 18 p. 33 cm. (Box 3)
  - A bit of half-forgotten history: [an account of Indian massacre of troops led by Colonel Archibald Laughery in Dearborn County, Ind. 1781., Carbon of Typed Document 4 p. 27 cm. (Box 3)
  - Brindley, Mrs. L. J., Vevay, Ind. Biographical scketch of Evelyn M. Craig., Typed Document 2 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Xerox copy.
  - Coulter, James, 1836-, soldier. Autobiographical account, 1836-1865., n.d. -; Autograph Document pp. 1-24, 201. 24 cm. (Box 3)
    Account for January 25, 1862-July 23, 1865 lacking. Served in Co. A, 37th regt., Indiana Volunteers.
  - Cunningham, J. B. Early churches and church work in Indiana., Typed Document 13 p. 33 cm. (Box 3)
  - Esarey, Logan, 1874-1942, historian. Address celebrating early Indiana masonry., Typed Document 9 pp. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Accompanied by L.S., George Robert Wilson, Indianapolis, Ind.
    To Logan Esarey, Bloomington, Ind., Feb. 15, 1924.
  - Genealogical charts showing ancestors of John Hampden Holliday., n.d. -; Autograph Document 4 pp. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Harrison, Benjamin, 1833-1901. Signatures on title pages of "Reports of Cases Argued and Determined in the Supreme Court of the State of Indiana," various editions., 4 mss. 23 cm. (Box 3)
    Removed to manuscript collection in 1980.
  - Hershman, William Handford, Columbus, Ind. A look into the dim past: [relating particularly to the building of roads and canals in Indiana], Typed Document 41 [i.e. 40] pp. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Accompanied by L.S., William Handford Hershman. to Logan Esarey, Dec. 25, 1923.
  - Historical Points of interest in Indiana., Document 9 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Relates particularly to La Salle's explorations and early French posts.
  - History of La Porte, Ind., Document 19 p. 26-28 cm. (Box 3)
    Incomplete. Includes typewritten pages numbered 5-12, with chapter headings "The first white inhabitants" and "Building the Town;" and handwritten pates, numbered 28-38, headed "Under the city charter."
  - Indiana 1816, a map., Document 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    "Edward M. Hale" signed in lower right-hand corner.
  - Isham, William S., 1898-1961, lawyer. Photograph of George Ade and "Bo" McMillin., 16.3 x 21.4 cm. (Box 3)
    Note on verso idientifies photographer and subjects.
    George Ade with straw hat and cane.
    McMillin, football coach at Indiana University between 1934-1947
    Accompanied by transmittal letter from George Alonzo Wright, Class of 1919, A.P.I., to Henry William Hofstetter, dated 28 Sept 1984. (Autograph Letter Signed 6 pp. 27.5 cm).
  - Jones, John Hewitt, 1814-1882, merchant, steamboat clerk, real estate agent. The autobiography of John H. Jones, 1814-1882: life in Rising Sun, Ind.; as a steamboat clerk on the Ohio River; removal of the Creek Indians from Georgia to Indian territory in the winter of 1835., Typed copy. 9 p. 35 cm. (Box 3)
    Contains also photostat of the mss. music of "Arkansaw … played on the violin by a half breed Indian (Creek) on the S. B. Alpha while removing them from their old home in Georgia in winter of 1835 to their New Home in Indian. Ter." "Wrote by memory by John H. Jones. Winter-1835.' (1 p. 13 cm.)
    (Appended note: "[Not to be published without permission of Indiana State Library]").
    Purchase. 1937
  - Knox, Julia Le Clerc, 1871?-1965, educator, author. Vevay, Ind. Transportation in Indiana., Typed Document 14 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Koch, Felix John, 1882-1933, writer. The last of the Miamis [in Miami County, Ind.], Typed Document 5 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Lockridge, Ross Franklin, 1877-1952, writer. The Boat Load of Knowledge. The Trip Down the River., n.d. -; Typed (Carbon) Signed 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Bears additional notes in ink.
    Transferred from Howard Ship Yards & Dock Co. mss. 1983
  - Morgan, Will H., soldier, medicine salesman. To "Dear Father & Mother". Reports on his safe arrival among friends, comments on the local people and weather, Alvin Hobbs is holding [a] meeting here now", and hopes to secure a job soon., Autograph Letter Signed 1 p. 25 cm. (Box 3)
    Dated: Monday Morning, 26th
  - Notes on Baynard Ruch Hall's New Purchase., n.d. -; Autograph Document 2 p. 36 cm. (Box 3)
    Unsigned.
    Gives page references to the New York, Appleton, 1843 edition of Hall's New Purchase … in 2 volumes.
    Gift. Source unknown. 1936
  - Oglesbee, Rollo B., fl. 1908, author, and; Hale, Albert Barlow, 1860- 1929, compiler. History of Michigan City, Indiana., Autograph Document & Typed Document 359 p. 8-28 cm. (Box 3)
    [1] Chapters 1-13. (Typed Document 281 p. 28 cm.)
    [2] Parts of chapters 1 & 3. (Autograph Document 68 p. 15-22 cm.)
    [3] Notes for the history. (Autograph Document 46 p. 8-22 cm.)
  - Owen, Robert Dale, 1801-1877, social reformer. To "Annie". Thanks her for note and visit. Says he is better but not well. Will call on her soon., Autograph Letter Signed 3 p. 13 cm. (Box 3)
  - Photographs of the Colonel William Jones House, Gentryville, Ind., and the James Cochran House, Bloomington, Ind., 10 photos. 20.5 x 25.5 cm. (Box 3)
    Size: 8 x 10 inches.
    Photographer's name not given.
    Jones House: 6 photos, accompanied by leaflet stating house was constructed in 1834.
    Cochran House: 4 photos, accompanied by leaflet stating house was constructed in 1850.
    With the photos is leaflet describing the English and American Homes Exhibit for which the photographs were used in Summer, 1979, at the Lilly Library.
  - A sketch of the Madison, Ind. schools, 1810-1915., Typed Document 17 p. 33 cm. (Box 3)
  - Smith, Mrs. Katherine M., Clubwoman. Indiana's Art Historian: Mrs. Harry Bentley Burnet, Typed Document (carbon) 8 p. 22 cm. (Box 3)
    Read before the Indiana chapter of the National Society of the Arts and Letters.
  - Stephenson, David Curtis, 1891-1966, klansman. D. C. Stephenson, 302-5 Kresge Bldg., Indianapolis, Indiana. To "My Faithful Friends". Refers to state democratic convention., Typed Letter 1 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Stephenson, David Curtis, 1891-1966, klansman. Manifesto issued in … fight against Walter F. Bossert. Includes excerpts from the constitution and by-laws of the Knights of the Ku Klux Klan and a copy of a letter from Hiram Wesley Evans, imperial wizard, of Atlanta, Georgia, to David Curtis Stephenson, dated August 2, 1923., Copy of Typed Document 21 p. 36 cm. (Bound 59)
  - Stevens, Stephen C., -1870, laywer. Youthful studies: law notes., n.d. -; Autograph Document Signed 552 p. 21 cm. (Bound 60)
    Binder's title: Steven's Law Brief, vol. 2
  - Stewart, John Lee, 1910-, zoologist. A way away: an autobiography of John Lee Stewart, negro, of life in Tennessee, in Indianapolis, Ind., at Butler University, and at Indiana University., Typed Document 381 p. 29 cm. (Bound 61)
  - Theodore Franz Sigel., n.d. -; Autograph Document 9 p. 21 cm. (Box 3)
  - Turner, J. F., 1870?-. Tuscola, Illinois. Recollections of the Cleveland-Harrison Campaign of 1888 in Putnam County, Indiana., Typed Document 5 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Vestal, John, 1832-, merchant. Autobiography., n.d. -; Typed Document 31 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
    Accompanied by: Copy of a printed genealogy of the Vestal family from 1683-1893 issued in 1893. (Typed Document 7 p. 28 cm.)
  - Walker, Kenneth Roland, 1928-, educator. A man and a township: Jackson Township, Elkhart County, Ind., and the reminiscences of Charles A. Neff., Typed Document 20 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - White, Frank Allan. The Wabash-Erie canal suit., n.d. -; Typed Document 4 p. 28 cm. (Box 3)
  - Wilder Brigade Monument at Chickamauga National Military Park: photograph, n.d. (Box 3)
    Dedication ceremony held Sept. 20, 1899. Monument to the achievements of the Lightning Brigade of the 17th Indiana under General John Thomas Wilder, 1830-1917. Accompanied by a clipping of part of the same photo. References: Indiana Magazine of History 31:169-203 for article about Wilder by S.C. Williams (Lilly F521.I395); Indiana at Chickamauga, 1863-1900, Indianapolis, 1901 (Lilly E475.81 .I39) page 310 for photo view
  - [Women's rights movement in Indiana in the 1840's and 1850's]., Typed Document [44] leaves. (Box 3)
    Title-page and page 11 missing.
  - Wylie, T.A. Notes and comments analyzing... (Box 3)